Heiner Andrés Solano Arguedas

Costa Rica Heredia +506 64040376 heiner.andres@outlook.com

SYSTEMS ENGINEER

Proactive professional with extensive experience in the field of technology, programming languages and software development. With a focus on achieving goals and obtaining results, complete the process of creating and configuring software environments, committed to delivering an updated and quality product.

Stacks:

- ✓ Windows, C# Web, Desktop, Apis, WCF, Azure.
- ✓ Web, Angular, NodeJS, React, Django.
- ✓ <u>Data bases</u>, Sql, Oracle, Postgresql.
- ✓ Analytics and data science, Python.

WORK EXPERIENCE (5 years)

Novacomp

February 2022 – November 2022

Systems Engineer

Implement new functionalities in software, defining requirements, create functionalities and launch in production environments.

Technologies: C# Windows Forms WCF, SQLServer.

Grupo Babel

October 2020 - February 2022

Systems Engineer

Create web functionalities, joining meetings to raise requirements, create functionalities and deploy in the indicated environments.

Technologies: C# MVC Rest Api, SQLServer.

Optimized Data Solutions

August 2016 – January 2018

Systems Engineer

Develop new modules in banking applications, adding dynamic interfaces, display data from the database and create reports in different formats.

Technologies: C# MVC WCF, SQL.

Seidor

March 2015 – June 2016

Systems Engineer

Technical consulting of the WM module in an SAP implementation, creation of a soap service to communicate between SAP ERP and the application that we after create in Android Studio that reads barcodes for the sale, entry and movement of products between warehouses.

Technologies: Python, Android Studio, Java, Postgresgl.

EDUCATION

- **Universidad Nacional,** Heredia, Costa Rica. Information Systems Engineering (2018).
- **Invenio-Sykes**, San José, Costa Rica. English for Employability Program (2020).